thinksales.co.za 2013-05-03

# Privacy Policy | ThinkSales

## Overview

The privacy of our visitors and members is very important to us. Since we do gather information about you, we provide this privacy statement to enable you to understand the terms and conditions associated with the collection of this data, as well as how we use it and how you can correct or change it. In addition, we make the following pledge to you:

## Thinksales.co.za Privacy Pledge

  * The information we collect about you and/or your business will be used for purposes of site research and development in an effort to better serve your needs.
  * We will never contact you without your permission, and we will immediately terminate any communications with you upon request.
  * When uploading your personal information on our portal you agree to allow ThinkSales Corporation (Pty) Ltd full access and rights to your information.
  * ThinkSales (Pty) Ltd will take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information and for the purpose of this clause, “personal information” shall be defined as detailed in the Promotion of Access to Information Act 2 of 2000 (PAIA).
  * ThinkSales retain the right, with your consent, for the duration of your subscription to share your information with a third party at the discretion of ThinkSales Corporation (Pty) Ltd relating to recruitment on our portal, this right includes disseminating information for statistical and market research purposes.

## Electronic Newsletters

You can choose to subscribe to our free electronic newsletters.

These newsletters are distributed through our list manager. To subscribe, simply click on the “Subscribe to e-newsletter” link and provide necessary details and then submit. From time to time, you may be asked to provide additional information.

As a subscriber to our newsletter, you also agree to receive advertisements, promotions and special communications from ThinkSales and its partners.

You can remove yourself from our newsletter e-mail lists by simply following the “Unsubscribe” directions included in each newsletter.

Please be assured that information you voluntarily give us will not be shared with any third party beyond our list manager without your consent.

## Usage Reports

In order to better understand traffic patterns on any site owned and operated by ThinkSales.co.za, we analyse our site activity to obtain overall usage statistics. These usage statistics provide us with certain information obtained from data within the browser string (information contained in every user’s browser). Information we collect from the browser string includes domain name, browser type, operating system and MIME type.

## E-mail Data Analysis

From time to time, we provide our e-mail lists (newsletters and special offers) to third party companies who provide specialised services, such as e-mail message deployment, merge-purge (identifying and removing duplicate addresses) of lists, statistical analysis and other data processing.

## Cookies

All sites owned and operated by ThinkSales use cookies. A cookie is a small data file written to your hard drive. Cookies allow us to understand user behaviour so that we can more effectively develop information and programmes to serve you better. Advertisers require information regarding ad impressions and click-through rates, and by providing them with this information, we are able to keep our sites FREE to our visitors.

If you are concerned about the use of cookies, you have the option to set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, or to turn off cookies entirely. The options to warn or disable cookies can be found in the “Options” or “Preferences” feature of your browser.

YOU DO NOT NEED TO ENABLE COOKIES IN ORDER TO USE ANY SITE OWNED AND OPERATED BY THINKSALES.

## Beacons

Like many websites, ThinkSales may also use pixel tags, also known as beacons, spotlight tags or web bugs, to improve our understanding of site traffic, visitor behaviour and response to promotional campaigns, as a supplement to our server logs and other methods of traffic and response measurement. We may also implement pixel tags provided by other companies for the same purpose.

## Links to Other Sites

Please be aware that when you are on ThinkSales.co.za or any site owned by ThinkSales, or when you receive an e-mail message from us on behalf of a marketer according to permission granted through our opt-in process for newsletters and special offers, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control, such as the marketer’s site. There may be links to other sites from ThinkSales.co.za pages or from the e-mail message we send to you that take you outside ThinkSales.co.za.

These other sites may send their own cookies to visitors, collect data or solicit personal information. The privacy policies of these other sites may be significantly different from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there.

## Security

Protecting the security of your personal information is very important to us. When we store information you have provided to us, that information is protected by security measures that include “firewalls” (a combination of computer hardware and software that helps keep unauthorised visitors from accessing information within our computer network). As a result, while ThinkSales.co.za strives to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible and/or liable for the theft, destruction or inadvertent disclosure of your personal information by direct or indirect use of our website.

## Correcting Information

You can correct or update any information you have provided to ThinkSales.co.za by following the instructions in any electronic newsletter or offering we send.

Alternatively, you may correct your information by emailing our webmaster.

## Deactivating

Any user receiving our electronic newsletter may opt out of our e-mail list at any time by simply following the instructions to “Unsubscribe” within each newsletter.

## Changes to the ThinkSales Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time. If there is a significant change, we will indicate on our sites that our privacy policy has changed and provide a link to the new policy.

## Contacting ThinkSales

Should you have any questions, concerns or suggestions, you may contact ThinkSales.co.za by emailing our webmaster.

Comments are closed.
